 href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Playfair+Display:wght@400;700;900
 What Exactly is Artificial Intelligence?</span><span
>What Exactly is Artificial Intelligence?</div>
   <p>How does a computer become "smart"? It doesn't go to school. Instead, AI le
ne million pictures</span> of apple pies?</p>
      <p>Ready to see the magic? The easiest way to try AI is by downloa
 at a blank text box. What do you do now? In AI, the instruction you type
            minutes? Give me step-by-step instructions."</sp
            a gentle 3-day itinerary?"</span></p>
rom the doctor with a confusing pamphlet? Type the terms into your AI app: <span
        <p>Traveling abroad? Your phone can listen to spoken Spanish
   <p>Find a strange weed in your garden? Take a picture of the leaves with your 
        <p>Fixing a leaky faucet? Describe the problem or snap a photo, a
        <p>AI for recipes or poems? Hallucinations don't matter. But for fi
          Really You?"</div>
          "What's the safe-word?" A scammer won't know it.</p>
le">Privacy ù What Does AI Know About Me?</div>
s like a private conversation. But is it?</p>
d #e0ddd6; font-size:14px; color:#333;">? Do not type your
d #e0ddd6; font-size:14px; color:#333;">? Do not share banking
d #e0ddd6; font-size:14px; color:#333;">? Do not share highly
ing:8px 0; font-size:14px; color:#333;">? For financial doc review ù delete your 
e="font-size:48px; margin-bottom:18px;">?</div>
